<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"> <id>/</id><title>Unrivaled Rōnin</title><subtitle>CyberSecurity, Threat Intelligence, Life, Incident Response and Threat.</subtitle> <updated>2023-12-25T22:23:22+07:00</updated> <author> <name>Aung 🥷🏻</name> <uri>/</uri> </author><link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="/feed.xml"/><link rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" href="/"/> <generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.2">Jekyll</generator> <rights> © 2023 Aung 🥷🏻 </rights> <icon>/assets/img/favicons/favicon.ico</icon> <logo>/assets/img/favicons/favicon-96x96.png</logo> <entry><title>3 Practical Productivity Books to Transform Our Lives</title><link href="/posts/PracticalProductivityBooks/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="3 Practical Productivity Books to Transform Our Lives" /><published>2023-07-15T14:45:00+07:00</published> <updated>2023-07-15T14:45:00+07:00</updated> <id>/posts/PracticalProductivityBooks/</id> <content src="/posts/PracticalProductivityBooks/" /> <author> <name>aung</name> </author> <category term="Notes" /> <category term="Productivity" /> <summary> Google “productivity books” and it gives a handful list of books. As an avid productivity explorer, I read a good amount of them, and most of them definitely deliver useful messages to the audience. If I have to pick 3 books that most people can apply to their daily work and lives, it narrows down the following 3 books that have practical methods and approaches to tackle our personal and work... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Free Useful AI model based Tools in 2023</title><link href="/posts/AITools/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Free Useful AI model based Tools in 2023" /><published>2023-06-26T11:45:00+07:00</published> <updated>2023-06-26T11:45:00+07:00</updated> <id>/posts/AITools/</id> <content src="/posts/AITools/" /> <author> <name>aung</name> </author> <category term="Notes" /> <category term="Productivity" /> <summary> In 2023, we are witnessing a fast-growing market of value-added services on top of AI models, thanks in part to the availability of OpenAI’s ChatGPT to the public. With so many services available, it can be difficult to determine which ones are worth your time and effort. In this post, I’ll share some free services that you can use to improve your productivity and workflow. Please note that whi... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Systems Thinking Applied to Cybersecurity</title><link href="/posts/systems-thinking/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Systems Thinking Applied to Cybersecurity" /><published>2023-06-11T10:45:00+07:00</published> <updated>2023-06-11T10:45:00+07:00</updated> <id>/posts/systems-thinking/</id> <content src="/posts/systems-thinking/" /> <author> <name>aung</name> </author> <category term="Security" /> <category term="Theory" /> <summary> Connected Leadership to Systems Thinking At the time of writing this, I am taking a Coursea course on Connected Leadership that explores how to make changes from the individual, team, and system levels. It’s a recommended course for anyone who wants to improve their systematic thinking and learn how to think better. Section 3 of the course is about systems thinking, and I am trying to underst... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Boost Productivity with These Tools in 2023</title><link href="/posts/productivity-2023/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Boost Productivity with These Tools in 2023" /><published>2023-06-11T10:45:00+07:00</published> <updated>2023-06-11T10:45:00+07:00</updated> <id>/posts/productivity-2023/</id> <content src="/posts/productivity-2023/" /> <author> <name>aung</name> </author> <category term="Notes" /> <category term="Productivity" /> <summary> I am avid enthusiast of productivity hack and wrote a few pieces over the past years on my productivity system and how to connect the digital apps that I used in a daily basis. This past few weeks, I discovered an approach that have been talking over productivity hack YouTuber and creators about building a backup or 2nd brain and the implementation of it. This post is to highlight my findings a... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>ChatGPT Use Cases for CyberSecurity Folks</title><link href="/posts/chatgpt/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="ChatGPT Use Cases for CyberSecurity Folks" /><published>2023-04-12T01:45:00+07:00</published> <updated>2023-04-12T01:45:00+07:00</updated> <id>/posts/chatgpt/</id> <content src="/posts/chatgpt/" /> <author> <name>aung</name> </author> <category term="Security" /> <category term="AI" /> <summary> A Recap on ChatGPT and Alternatives Currently, there are numerous ChatGPT and alternative NLP-based technologies available, such as Anthropic, GPT-3, and WebGPT. The list of more than 600 apps can be found at gpt3demo, and it continues to grow. A few I personally used are Poe by Quora, Perplexity, AI21 Labs and Flowrite. I wrote this piece in a way of exploring how this NLP technology can assi... </summary> </entry> </feed>
